[{"answer": "No, never -- never in a million years.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Have you ever thought you were going to be world famous for cross dressing?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Are you nervous?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Oh, abused his entire life.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "He had been abused?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "I found it out by asking questions, finally, of him, because I was talking to him --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "How did you find this out?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "He told me a lot about it.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "So, he told you?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes, he's still alive.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Is he still alive, your father?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "We don't speak very much, but I am taking care of him.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "And what kind of relationship do you have with him?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "You support him?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "No, I never felt that.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Do you think despite the way that he -- he manhandled you and beat you and so on, did you feel that he loved you?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "-- so that was another thing I didn't know, which caused a lot of issues, as well.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "I did, about four years ago, I asked, why.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Did you have that out with him?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I think so, because he -- in any situation, he's in tears.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Is he proud of you, for what you've achieved?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Listen, that's exactly what I thought very early on.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Is that guilt, do you think?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "No, he hasn't.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Has he ever said sorry?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "At this point, I don't know if it matters.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Would you like him to?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "She -- it -- well, you mean of all the success?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "-- get her a red Jaguar?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Just -- she's speechless, just a thank you and the love.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "The same as you come before me more than you go to the doctor, for a checkup.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "How you doing?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "You don't know me.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Who you think you're talking to, old lady?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Yes, never --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Did you ever think, when you were young and you -- you thought of treading the boards that one day you'd be world famous for cross dressing?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "It's about strong women.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "There are lots of other Madeas from every -- I've met a Jewish Madea, I've met an Italian Madea, you know?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Any comment?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I just try -- it drives me insane.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "You feel uncomfortable talking about money?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "No, who wants to show -- it's not a -- it's certainly not about showing off.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "-- show off about it?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Again, the best thing which is -- which changed my entire life was being able to support my mother.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What is the best thing about money, though, for you?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, because it's -- I just feel that to whom much is given, much is required.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Why do you -- why do you feel awkward talking about this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "My faith.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "How have you avoided the pitfalls that go with superstar fame, big money and all the rest of it?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "And I say no, but it's a very particular pressure?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "I actually did.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Do you enjoy playing the action hero?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Mostly I worked with the trainers, Anthony Goldstein (ph), a great guy.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "How did you do it?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Because there are --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Once, yes.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I think we were both very young.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "And what went wrong?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yes, it was.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "It -- was it, in the end, your decision to walk away?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yes, because we both were in a place where -- and I just realized I should not have said this, because --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "You thought it was the right thing?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Because I said too much.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Why shouldn't you have said it?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "It's a fascinating side to you, because you're being so nice about it and -- and so honest.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Why don't you ask another question?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "And what's the rush?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Yes, I want that more than I want to be married, though.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "But don't you want little Tylers running around?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Yes, please.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Should we move on?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "No, it's all good.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Do you want have a glass of water?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no, no.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "-- were you thinking?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "To be honest with you, I did not.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Did you have any idea who she was?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "I -- I had heard of her, but I didn't know all of -- that she had done.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "You'd never heard of her?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "You supplied the plane, didn't you?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "No, no, I --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "The first black Bond?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "Will Smith should be the first black Bond.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "You reckon?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Because -- because --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Why should it be him?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "If you lose weight at the rate you're going, you'll be skinnier than Will Smith, no?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "There is one moment I'll -- I'll -- and I'll probably regret it for my entire life.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "-- to give you, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "I've been great.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 824, "question": "How have you been?", "qSentId": 823}, {"answer": "It really did.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 854, "question": "-- for years, and it really dragged you down, didn't it?", "qSentId": 853}, {"answer": "She told me to remember who I am.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 873, "question": "When times were really tough, when you were going through that hellish period, maybe doubting if you'd ever come back from it, what did you mother say to you?", "qSentId": 872}, {"answer": "It's pretty unbelievable.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 892, "question": "But do you ever stop and think wow, I'm still only 33 and yet I've had this 18-year career?", "qSentId": 891}, {"answer": "Oh my God.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "What's being a mother like?", "qSentId": 907}, {"answer": "One of the things that I can't -- I can't put my mind around is where she really was because, you know, at the end of her life, I wasn't there.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 950, "question": "Or had she just got lost in the maelstrom of fame and abuse and all the rest of it?", "qSentId": 949}, {"answer": "Oh, my God.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 957, "question": "As somebody who still can, do you understand what that feeling must be like?", "qSentId": 956}, {"answer": "I was actually in the same hotel that she passed in.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 971, "question": "How did you hear it?", "qSentId": 970}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 973, "question": "At the Beverly Hilton?", "qSentId": 972}, {"answer": "It hit me -- it just hit me in ways I can't even explain.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 986, "question": "It hit you that bad?", "qSentId": 985}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 999, "question": "Are you excited about having a new album out now, with everything that you've been through in the last 10 years?", "qSentId": 998}, {"answer": "I feel everything.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1006, "question": "When you sing, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 1005}, {"answer": "Oh, my love life is great.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1014, "question": "And how's your love life?", "qSentId": 1013}, {"answer": "We met at a studio, at a studio.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1023, "question": "Where did you meet?", "qSentId": 1022}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1026, "question": "On this is the one you think?", "qSentId": 1025}, {"answer": "That's it.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1032, "question": "RANDY: That's it?", "qSentId": 1031}, {"answer": "Let me see --", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1035, "question": "Is there anything else you want to say?", "qSentId": 1034}, {"answer": "No, we covered everything.", "docId": "121228pmt", "aSentId": 1037, "question": "Want to talk about world affairs?", "qSentId": 1036}]